Seira Yasumatsu

Creative problem solver and goal oriented product designer who identifies the right problem to solve and thrives to provide design experiences with empathy for the real users.

CONTACT

415.606.2993

≤ seiray117@gmail.com

SanFrancisco, CA

<u>seirayasumatsu.com</u>

in linkedin

github.com

AWARDS

Sodexo Scholarship

San Francisco State University November 2017

Stanford Design Challenge

Stanford center of longevity April 2018

SKILLS

Visual Design
UX/UI Design
User Research & Testing
Personas & User Stories
Brand Strategy & Identity
Information Architecture
Wireframes
Prototyping & Usability Testing

TOOLS

Adobe Creative Suite
Figma
InVision
Maze
HTML, CSS, & JavaScript
GitHub
Balsamiq
SolidWorks & Rhino3D

PROJECTS

behub | iOS Prototype and Marketing Site

Designed to help users to manage and organize a family's schedule and content by collaborating among family members. Used Invision and Maze for user research and testing and Figma for prototyping. behub

STEMA++ | Web Prototype and wearable device prototype

Designed a platform for educators, parents, and girls to create a STEM community with wearable devices. Web Prototype created with Adobe XD and Adobe Creative Suite.

EDUCATION

Bloc | 2018-2019

User Experience & Front End Development Apprenticeship

San Francisco State University | Class of 2018

BS in Industrial Design

Diablo Valley College | Class of 2012

AS in Early Childhood Education

EXPERIENCE

Bloc

UX Design & Front End Development Apprenticeship I 2018—present

- Designed and developed iOS and web prototype using Figma and Adobe Suite
- Conducted user-surveys with 40 potential users and performed survey analysis
- Created a design guide style that was used across multi-platforms
- Packaged deliverables to hand off to an engineering team
- Developed a responsive and intuitive website by using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript

Stanford Center of Longevity Design Challenge

UX/Product Design I Sep 2017—April 2018

- Designed and developed a versatile garden station following the design process
- Iterated the design based on user research, user feedback, and user testing
- Designed and delivered visual and graphical presentations for over 100 people

Growing Light Montessori School

Early Childhood Educator & Creative Director I Mar 2010—May 2014

- Implemented activities, toys, and materials based on children's interest and needs
- Planned and introduced a better design system for the afternoon-care transition